Well, the next three riders in the order,
那么，接下来的三位车手按顺序，
you know, of Vingar and the two Red Bulls,
你知道的，Vingar和两辆红牛的车手，
were on time trial bikes.
都骑的是计时赛用车。
The Bremko Avanapal, who was the notable absentee, really,
Bremko Avanapal，这位值得注意的缺席车手，说真的，
ended up 12th, having been second fastest through the first split,
最终排名第12，在第一个分段计时中曾是第二快的，
which would have been where the time trial bike
而那正是计时赛用车能发挥最大优势的地方，
would have had the maximum advantage and it all went backwards for him from then on.
能发挥最大优势的地方，而从那之后他的表现就一落千丈了。
But the second, third and fourth road time trial bikes, the winner, the dominant winner,
但第二、第三和第四位车手骑的是公路计时赛用车，而冠军，那个统治级的冠军，
I sort of think Pogacar could have done virtually any, you know,
我觉得波加查几乎可以做任何事，你知道，
could have gone up there on a Brompton and he probably would have won the time trial.
就算骑一辆Brompton上去，他可能也能赢得这场计时赛。
We saw Renko the other day there at the back and I got in contact with the team and said,
我们前几天在后面看到了Renko，我联系了车队并说，
why is he at the back? Why is he off the back?
他为什么在后面？他为什么掉队了？
And he's just going back to the team car. There's something not right with Renko.
他只是在回到车队的车那里。Renko肯定出了什么问题。
He's not quite firing.
他没有完全发挥出水平。
And he was almost humiliated in the time 12 yesterday.
而且他昨天的计时赛几乎很狼狈。
So let's see how he gets on today.
所以我们看看他今天的表现如何。
I cannot think that for one moment he will be good today.
我一刻也不觉得他今天会表现好。
Well, crunching the numbers and Kieran Kelly is with the statistics.
嗯，现在来分析数据，Kieran Kelly负责统计。
Gives him some fantastic, really left field, some oddballed statistics.
给他一些很棒的，非常离谱的，一些奇怪的统计数据。
But one that he's working on at the moment.
但他现在正在研究其中一个（数据）。
And we haven't got an absolute definitive clear certain answer.
而且我们还没有得到一个绝对明确、肯定的答案。
But we believe that that's the first time that a reigning world time trial champion
但我们认为这是现任世界计时赛冠军
has ever been caught in a time trial.
有史以来首次在计时赛中被抓。
And this Vingo catching him for two minutes yesterday.
而Vingo昨天领先了他两分钟。
It's 95% sure on that one.
那件事有95%的把握。
Yeah, we might have had something maybe in the past.
是的，我们过去可能也有过类似情况。
I can't remember.
我不记得了。
Maybe in a prologue I can remember some stuff that was...
也许在序幕赛段，我记得一些事情是...
Important work working that one out.
要弄清楚那件事需要做重要的工作。
Cruising off the front of the moment.
此刻正轻松骑行在前方。
The Little Shracks have certainly been much in evidence in the early attacks.
在早期的攻击中，The Little Shracks 无疑十分突出。
Quinn Simmons, Atis Gilmose and others.
Quinn Simmons、Atis Gilmose 等人。
It's a good one that they have.
他们拥有的这个很不错。
Trek notable really by having a bespoke water bottle.
Trek 确实因拥有一个定制水壶而引人注目。
Gives them a little bit of an aerodynamic advantage.
这给他们带来了一点空气动力学优势。